James Kolbe Papers, 1958-2006 (bulk 1985-2006)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup 2: Congressional Activities, 1980-2006
  - Legislative Activity Files, Series 2: 1984-2006
    - 107th Congress, 1989-2005
      - H.R. 1140- The Railroad and Survivors' Improvement Act, 2000-2001 (Box 78, Folder 17)
      - H.R. 1331- Fair Care for the Uninsured Act, 2001 (Box 78, Folder 18)
      - H.R. 1701- Consumer Rental Agreement Act, 2002-2003 (Box 78, Folder 19)
      - H.R. 1774- Small Business Health Fairness Act, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 20)
      - H.R. 1807- Immigrant Labor Policy Review Act, 2001 (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - H.R. 2073- TRICARE Retirees Opportunity Act, 2001 (Box 79, Folder 2)
      - H.R. 2234- Tumacacori National Park Boundary Revision Act, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 3)
      - H.R. 2269- The Retirement Security Advice Act, 2001 (Box 79, Folder 4)
      - H.R. 2356- Bipartisan Campaign Reform Act, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 5)
      - H.R. 2528- Legal Tender Modernization Act (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 79, Folder 6)
      - H.R. 2528- Legal Tender Modernization Act (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 79, Folder 7)
      - H.R. 2620- Veterans' Affairs-Housing and Urban Development Appropriations, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 8)
      - H.R. 2646- Farm Security Act of 2001 (1 of 4), 2001-2004 (Box 79, Folder 9)
      - H.R. 2646- Farm Security Act of 2001 (2 of 4), 2001-2004 (Box 79, Folder 10)
      - H.R. 2646- Farm Security Act of 2001 (3 of 4), 2001-2004 (Box 79, Folder 11)
      - H.R. 2646- Farm Security Act of 2001 (4 of 4), 2001-2004 (Box 79, Folder 12)
      - H.R. 2770- Transparency and Fairness Trade Act, 2001-2004 (Box 79, Folder 13)
      - H.R. 2806- Bob Stump Department of Veterans Affairs Medical Center, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 14)
      - H.R. 2887- Best Pharmaceuticals for Children Act, 2001 (Box 79, Folder 15)
      - H.R. 2944- Fiscal Year 2002 District of Columbia Appropriations Act, 2001-2002 (Box 79, Folder 16)
      - H.R. 3109- Medicare Ambulance Payment Reform Act, 2001 (Box 79, Folder 17)
      - H.R. 3195- To Extend the Medicare Community Nursing Organization (CNO) Demonstration Project, 2001 (Box 79, Folder 18)
      - H.R. 3210- The Terrorism Risk Protection Act, 2001-2002 (Box 79, Folder 19)
      - H.R. 3424- The Community Choice in Real Estate Act (1 of 2), 2001-2002 (Box 79, Folder 20)
      - H.R. 3424- The Community Choice in Real Estate Act (2 of 2), 2001-2002 (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - H.R. 3487- Nurse Reinvestment Act, 2001-2002 (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - H.R. 3684- Immediate Helping Hand Prescription Drug Assistance Act, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 3)
      - H.R. 3762- Pension Security Act, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 4)
      - H.R. 3763- Corporate and Auditing Accountability and Responsibility Act, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 5)
      - H.R. 3776- Illegal Immigrant Emergency Care Reimbursement Improvement Act, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 6)
      - H.R. 3925- Digital Tech Corps Act, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 7)
      - H.R. 4600- Medicare Malpractice, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 8)
      - H.R. 4737- Personal Responsibility, Work and Family Promotion Act (1 of 2), 2002 (Box 80, Folder 9)
      - H.R. 4737- Personal Responsibility, Work and Family Promotion Act (2 of 2), 2002 (Box 80, Folder 10)
      - H.R. 4967- Border Commuter Student Act (1 of 3), 2002 (Box 80, Folder 11)
      - H.R. 4967- Border Commuter Student Act (2 of 3), 2002 (Box 80, Folder 12)
      - H.R. 4967- Border Commuter Student Act (3 of 3), 2002 (Box 80, Folder 13)
      - H.R. 5005- Homeland Security Act (1 of 2), 2002 (Box 80, Folder 14)
      - H.R. 5005- Homeland Security Act (2 of 2), 2002 (Box 80, Folder 15)
      - H.R. 5121- Legislative Branch Appropriations Bill, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 16)
      - H.R. 5235- Former Prisoners of War Special Compensation Act (1 of 2), 2001-2002 (Box 80, Folder 17)
      - H.R. 5235- Former Prisoners of War Special Compensation Act (2 of 2), 2001-2002 (Box 80, Folder 18)
      - Immigrant Labor Policy Review Act, 2001 (Box 80, Folder 19)
      - Indian Gaming Regulatory Act (1 of 2), 1998-2001 (Box 81, Folder 1)
      - Indian Gaming Regulatory Act (2 of 2), 1998-2001 (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - International Boundary and Water Commission, 1999 (Box 81, Folder 3)
      - International education, 2001 (Box 81, Folder 4)
      - KC- 135E Airplane, 2001-2003 (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - LINK program, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 6)
      - Marana, 2000-2002 (Box 81, Folder 7)
      - Medical privacy, 2001-2002 (Box 81, Folder 8)
      - Medical Saving Accounts, 1997-2001 (Box 81, Folder 9)
      - Medicare, 2001-2002 (Box 81, Folder 10)
      - Medicare Modernization and Prescription Drug Act, 2002-2003 (Box 81, Folder 11)
      - Military, 2001-2002 (Box 81, Folder 12)
      - Military tribunals, 2001-2003 (Box 81, Folder 13)
      - National Forest Organizational Camp Fee Improvement Act, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 14)
      - Navy area theater ballistic missile defense system, 2001-2002 (Box 81, Folder 15)
      - One Dollar Coin Act, 1998-2001 (Box 81, Folder 16)
      - Organ donation program, 1998-2001 (Box 81, Folder 17)
      - Patients' Bill of Rights Act, 2001 (Box 81, Folder 18)
      - Pension reform- Enron, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 19)
      - Proposal for University of Arizona United States-Mexico Institute, 2001 (Box 81, Folder 20)
      - Proposition 204 Healthy Arizona Initiative, 2001 (Box 81, Folder 21)
      - Report to the House of Representatives Committee on Appropriations on Impacts caused by Undocumented Aliens crossing Federal Lands in Southeast Arizona, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Rural health care, 1998-2002 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - San Carlos Indian Irrigation Project, 1989-2001 (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - Section 3809- Surface Management Regulations, 2001 (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - Smith and Wesson Settlement Agreement, 2000-2001 (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - Social Security (1 of 4), 2001-2002 (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - Social Security (2 of 4), 2001-2002 (Box 82, Folder 7)
      - Social Security (3 of 4), 2001-2002 (Box 82, Folder 8)
      - Social Security (4 of 4), 2001-2002 (Box 82, Folder 9)
      - Sonoran Desert National Park Project (1 of 2), 1998-2002 (Box 82, Folder 10)
      - Sonoran Desert National Park Project (2 of 2), 1998-2002 (Box 82, Folder 11)
      - Space, 2001 (Box 82, Folder 12)
      - State Criminal Alien Assistance Program, 2001 (Box 82, Folder 13)
      - Steel industry sanctions, 2001-2002 (Box 82, Folder 14)
      - Support the Fort, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 15)
      - Tauzin-Dingell Bill H.R. 1542- The Internet Freedom and Broadband Deployment Act (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 82, Folder 16)
      - Tauzin-Dingell Bill H.R. 1542- The Internet Freedom and Broadband Deployment Act (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 83, Folder 1)
      - Telemedicine, 1998-2001 (Box 83, Folder 2)
      - Tohono O'odham Nation citizenship (1 of 2), 1998-2001 (Box 83, Folder 3)
      - Tohono O'odham Nation citizenship (2 of 2), 1998-2001 (Box 83, Folder 4)
      - Trade Adjustment Assistance, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 5)
      - Trade policy (1 of 2), 2001-2002 (Box 83, Folder 6)
      - Trade policy (2 of 2), 2001-2002 (Box 83, Folder 7)
      - Trade Promotion Authority (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 83, Folder 8)
      - Trade Promotion Authority (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 83, Folder 9)
      - Trauma centers, 2001 (Box 83, Folder 10)
      - Tucson Rod and Gun Club, 2001 (Box 83, Folder 11)
      - Tucson Soaring Club, 2001 (Box 83, Folder 12)
      - United Arab Emirates proposal for 162nd Fighter Wing, 2001 (Box 83, Folder 13)
      - United States-India Relations: Focus on trade, 2001 (Box 83, Folder 14)
      - United States Institute for Environmental Conflict Resolution, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 15)
      - United States-Mexico trans-boundary air quality, 1999-2002 (Box 83, Folder 16)
      - Unmanned aerial systems, 2002-2005 (Box 83, Folder 17)
      - Wildfires, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - 108th Congress, 1996-2005
      - 21st Century Retirement Security Act (1 of 4), 2002-2004 (Box 84, Folder 1)
      - 21st Century Retirement Security Act (2 of 4), 2002-2004 (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - 21st Century Retirement Security Act (3 of 4), 2002-2004 (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - 21st Century Retirement Security Act (4 of 4), 2002-2004 (Box 84, Folder 4)
      - Appropriations Bill- Department of Homeland Security Appropriations Bill, 2003-2004 (Box 84, Folder 5)
      - Appropriations Committee- appropriations requests, 2003-2004 (Box 84, Folder 6)
      - Appropriations Committee- Commerce, Justice, State, and the Judiciary, and related agencies, Fiscal Year 2005 Appropriations Bill (1 of 2), 2004 (Box 84, Folder 7)
      - Appropriations Committee- Commerce, Justice, State, and the Judiciary, and related agencies, Fiscal Year 2005 Appropriations Bill (2 of 2), 2004 (Box 84, Folder 8)
      - Appropriations Committee- Commerce, Justice, State, and the Judiciary, and related agencies, Small Business Association (1 of 2), 2003-2004 (Box 84, Folder 9)
      - Appropriations Committee- Commerce, Justice, State, and the Judiciary, and related agencies, Small Business Association (2 of 2), 2003-2004 (Box 84, Folder 10)
      - Appropriations Committee- Commerce, Justice, State, and the Judiciary Subcommittee, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 11)
      - Appropriations Committee- Department of Defense appropriations requests, 2002-2004 (Box 84, Folder 12)
      - Appropriations Committee- Department of Labor, Health and Human Services, and Education, and related agencies appropriations requests, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 13)
      - Appropriations Committee- District Five appropriations requests, 2004 (Box 84, Folder 14)
      - Appropriations Committee- Energy and Water Development Appropriations Bill, 2004 (Box 84, Folder 15)
      - Appropriations Committee- House Committee and Armed Services, Jim Kolbe appropriations requests, 2004 (Box 84, Folder 16)
      - Appropriations Committee- H.R. 4200, the National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2005, 2004 (Box 84, Folder 17)
      - Appropriations Committee- Labor, Health and Human Services appropriations requests, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - Appropriations Committee- Labor, Health, and Human Services, Education and related agencies Subcommittee, Jim Kolbe appropriations requests, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 2)
      - Appropriations Committee- Military Construction, 2004-2005 (Box 85, Folder 3)
      - Appropriations Committee- Military Construction Subcommittee, appropriations requests, 2002-2003 (Box 85, Folder 4)
      - Appropriations Committee- National Endowment for the Arts, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 5)
      - Appropriations Committee- National Park Service Budget (1 of 2), 2004 (Box 85, Folder 6)
      - Appropriations Committee- National Park Service Budget (2 of 2), 2004 (Box 85, Folder 7)
      - Appropriations Committee- Omnibus Appropriations Bill, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 8)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs (1 of 2), 2003-2004 (Box 85, Folder 9)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs (2 of 2), 2003-2004 (Box 85, Folder 10)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, Agriculture appropriations (1 of 2), 2002-2003 (Box 85, Folder 11)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, Agriculture appropriations (2 of 2), 2002-2003 (Box 85, Folder 12)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, appropriations requests (1 of 7), 2003-2004 (Box 85, Folder 13)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, appropriations requests (2 of 7), 2003-2004 (Box 85, Folder 14)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, appropriations requests (3 of 7), 2003-2004 (Box 85, Folder 15)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, appropriations requests (4 of 7), 2003-2004 (Box 85, Folder 16)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, appropriations requests (5 of 7), 2003-2004 (Box 86, Folder 1)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, appropriations requests (6 of 7), 2003-2004 (Box 86, Folder 2)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, appropriations requests (7 of 7), 2003-2004 (Box 86, Folder 3)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, funding requests (1 of 4), 2003 (Box 86, Folder 4)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, funding requests (2 of 4), 2003 (Box 86, Folder 5)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, funding requests (3 of 4), 2002 (Box 86, Folder 6)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, funding requests (4 of 4), 2004 (Box 86, Folder 7)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, Global HIV/AIDS initiative funds (1 of 2), 2004-2005 (Box 86, Folder 8)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, Global HIV/AIDS initiative funds (2 of 2), 2004-2005 (Box 86, Folder 9)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, H.R. 2800, Fiscal Year 2004 Appropriations Bill (1 of 4), 2003 (Box 86, Folder 10)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, H.R. 2800, Fiscal Year 2004 Appropriations Bill (2 of 4), 2003 (Box 86, Folder 11)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, H.R. 2800, Fiscal Year 2004 Appropriations Bill (3 of 4), 2003 (Box 86, Folder 12)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, H.R. 2800, Fiscal Year 2004 Appropriations Bill (4 of 4), 2003 (Box 86, Folder 13)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, Iraq and Afghanistan Reconstruction briefing book (1 of 3), 2003 (Box 86, Folder 14)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, Iraq and Afghanistan Reconstruction briefing book (2 of 3), 2003 (Box 86, Folder 15)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, Iraq and Afghanistan Reconstruction briefing book (3 of 3), 2003 (Box 86, Folder 16)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, Iraq Relief and Reconstruction Fund, 2003 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, Middle East partnership initiative, 2003-2005 (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, Migration and refugee assistance, 2002-2003 (Box 87, Folder 3)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, Millenium Challenge Account (1 of 3), 2004 (Box 87, Folder 4)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, Millenium Challenge Account (2 of 3), 2004 (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, Millenium Challenge Account (3 of 3), 2004 (Box 87, Folder 6)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, Millenium Challenge Corporation (1 of 3), 2004 (Box 87, Folder 7)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, Millenium Challenge Corporation (2 of 3), 2004 (Box 87, Folder 8)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, Millenium Challenge Corporation (3 of 3), 2004 (Box 87, Folder 9)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, Millenium Challenge Corporation, Armenia compact, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 10)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, Millenium Challenge Corporation briefing book, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 11)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, Millenium Challenge Corporation, Cape Verde compact, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 12)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, Millenium Challenge Georgia pact, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 13)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, USAID Microfinance Program, 2003 (Box 87, Folder 14)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, USAID/Mexico rural development activities, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 15)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, USAID (1 of 16), 2000-2004 (Box 87, Folder 16)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, USAID (2 of 16), 2000-2004 (Box 87, Folder 17)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, USAID (3 of 16), 2000-2004 (Box 88, Folder 1)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, USAID (4 of 16), 2000-2004 (Box 88, Folder 2)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, USAID (5 of 16), 2000-2004 (Box 88, Folder 3)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, USAID (6 of 16), 2000-2004 (Box 88, Folder 4)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, USAID (7 of 16), 2000-2004 (Box 88, Folder 5)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, USAID (8 of 16), 2000-2004 (Box 88, Folder 6)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, USAID (9 of 16), 2000-2004 (Box 88, Folder 7)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, USAID (10 of 16), 2000-2004 (Box 88, Folder 8)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, USAID (11 of 16), 2000-2004 (Box 88, Folder 9)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, USAID (12 of 16), 2000-2004 (Box 88, Folder 10)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, USAID (13 of 16), 2000-2004 (Box 88, Folder 11)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, USAID (14 of 16), 2000-2004 (Box 88, Folder 12)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, USAID (15 of 16), 2000-2004 (Box 88, Folder 13)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, USAID (16 of 16), 2000-2004 (Box 89, Folder 1)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, USAID Procurement System Improvement Project (1 of 2), 2000-2005 (Box 89, Folder 2)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing, and Related Programs, USAID Procurement System Improvement Project (2 of 2), 2000-2005 (Box 89, Folder 3)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on the Interior, Kolbe appropriations requests (1 of 2), 2004 (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on the Interior, Kolbe appropriations requests (2 of 2), 2004 (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on the Interior and related agencies, mark-up notes, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 6)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Transportation and the Treasury, Kolbe appropriation requests, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 7)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on Veterans Affairs, Housing and Urban Development, and independent agencies Appropriations Bill, Kolbe, Jim appropriations requests, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 8)
      - Appropriations Committee- Supplemental appropriations, 2003 (Box 89, Folder 9)
      - Appropriations Committee- UA-Housing and Urban Development appropriations requests, 2002-2004 (Box 89, Folder 10)
      - Appropriations Committee- University of Arizona funding requests, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 11)
      - April recess briefing book, 2003 (Box 89, Folder 12)
      - Arizona National Scenic Trail Feasibility Study Act, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 13)
      - Arizona transportation, 2003 (Box 89, Folder 14)
      - Arizona Water Settlements Act briefing, 2003 (Box 89, Folder 15)
      - Arizona Water Settlements Act briefing book, 2003 (Box 89, Folder 16)
      - Arthritis, 2003-2004 (Box 89, Folder 17)
      - Base realignment and closure, 2003-2004 (Box 90, Folder 1)
      - Bipartisan Retirement Security Act, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - Bipartisan Retirement Security Act, 2005 (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - Briefing books, 2003-2004 (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - Canamex, 1999-2004 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - Chinese defaulted bonds (1 of 2), 2002-2003 (Box 90, Folder 6)
      - Chinese defaulted bonds (2 of 2), 2002-2003 (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - Congressional Record Statements, 2003-2004 (Box 90, Folder 8)
      - Co-sponsor solicitation letters, incoming (1 of 3), 2003-2004 (Box 90, Folder 9)
      - Co-sponsor solicitation letters, incoming (2 of 3), 2003-2004 (Box 90, Folder 10)
      - Co-sponsor solicitation letters, incoming (3 of 3), 2003-2004 (Box 90, Folder 11)
      - District work period briefing book (1 of 2), January, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 12)
      - District work period briefing book (2 of 2), January, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 13)
      - District work period briefing book (1 of 2), August, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 14)
      - District work period briefing book (2 of 2), August, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - Education town hall briefing book, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - Federal Marriage Act (1 of 3), 2004 (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - Federal Marriage Act (2 of 3), 2004 (Box 91, Folder 4)
      - Federal Marriage Act (3 of 3), 2004 (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - Fort Huachuca (1 of 6), 2003-2004 (Box 91, Folder 6)
      - Fort Huachuca (2 of 6), 2003-2004 (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - Fort Huachuca (3 of 6), 2003-2004 (Box 91, Folder 8)
      - Fort Huachuca (4 of 6), 2003-2004 (Box 91, Folder 9)
      - Fort Huachuca (5 of 6), 2003-2004 (Box 91, Folder 10)
      - Fort Huachuca (6 of 6), 2003-2004 (Box 91, Folder 11)
      - Fort Huachuca, Black Officers Club restoration project, 2003 (Box 91, Folder 12)
      - Head Start, 2003-2004 (Box 91, Folder 13)